noahny.com 2019-12-18

# Privacy – Noah NYC

This policy (“Privacy Policy”) describes how the Website collects and uses the information of its users. Please read this Privacy Policy carefully, as it applies each time a user accesses the Website and uses its services, regardless of whether or not a purchase is made. By using and accessing the Website or registering and/or making purchases on the Website, you accept the terms of this Privacy Policy.

The Website is operated by Noah Clothing LLC. The words “user”, “you” and “your” in this Privacy Policy refer to a user of the Website. 

TYPES OF INFORMATION WE COLLECT FROM USERS AND HOW WE COLLECT IT:

When you use the Website, we may collect your (i) personal information (data that personally identifies you), or (ii) aggregate information, concerning your use of the Website and your account activity (e.g., number and times of log-ins, most frequently visited pages, IP address, etc.), which does not personally identify you.

The types of information we collect include:

· Information you provide to us. Information provided by registering on the Website, subscribing to our newsletter, making a purchase or contacting us through the Website or via email, including your name, address, email address, credit card information, and phone number.

· Automatically collected information. When you access our Website, some information not associated with specific users, such as device type, location information, IP address, webpage traffic, and access time is automatically collected in order to ensure the Website’s functionality. Automatic means of data collection include cookies and web beacons.

· Third party sources. We may collect information from third parties to whom you have provided your information, and consented to the sale, rental or transfer thereof (for example, through social media).

HOW WE USE YOUR INFORMATION:

Your information is processed using primarily electronic means and is used, without limitation, for the following services:

· Registration for an account or newsletter;

· Order fulfillment and related activities;

· Management of payments, including anti-fraud control when paying by credit/debit card;

· Marketing communications;

· Customization of content;

· Responding to customer service requests and similar communications from you; and

· Technical assistance.

HOW WE PROTECT YOUR INFORMATION:

The Website uses Secure Socket Layer (SSL) software and similar encrypting systems to protect your information when you purchase products on the Website. Only employees, contractors and agents of the Website operator may access user information on a need to know basis and only for the purposes set forth in this Privacy Policy.

While we make reasonable efforts to ensure your information is processed and stored in a secure manner, we cannot guarantee the security of data transferred over the Internet and you assume the risk of any such transfer. 

WHERE WE STORE YOUR INFORMATION:

Your information will be collected and stored in Shopify's secure data centers

SHARING YOUR INFORMATION:

We will not sell or otherwise disclose your information, except as described in this section and other relevant sections of this Privacy Policy.

· We may retain third party service providers in order to process your data in connection with the services provided on the Website (e.g., shipments, processing payments, logistics services, IT support, customer service or marketing communications). Third parties who perform these operations are only permitted to use the information provided to them to perform their function and for no other purpose. Please contact us at info@noahny.com to receive a full list of third party providers who may receive your information.

· In the event there is a change in the corporate structure of Noah Clothing LLC including, without limitation, by merger, consolidation, sale, liquidation, or transfer of substantial assets, we may, in our sole discretion, transfer, sell or assign users’ information collected on and through the Website to one or more affiliated or unaffiliated third parties or successor in interest.

· We may disclose a user’s information when required to do so to comply with applicable law or legal process or to respond to a request from law enforcement authorities. We may also provide your information where necessary for the defense of legal claims or for fraud prevention purposes.

LINKS TO THIRD PARTY SITES:

The Website contains links to third party websites, which we do not operate, control, monitor, endorse or guarantee. This Privacy Policy does not apply to the collection and use of information by such third party websites. We suggest that you carefully read the privacy policy and other policies of all third party websites.

We provide hyperlinks to third party websites only for the convenience of our users and is not a recommendation that users access such third party websites. We do not guarantee the services or goods provided and sold by such third party websites to Internet users. YOU AGREE THAT YOUR USE OF ANY THIRD PARTY WEBSITE IS AT YOUR SOLE RISK AND WITHOUT WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND BY NOAH CLOTHING LLC, EXPRESS, IMPLIED OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, WARRANTIES OF TITLE, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, MERCHANTABILITY OR NONINFRINGEMENT. UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES SHALL NOAH CLOTHING LLC BE LIABLE FOR DAMAGES ARISING FROM ANY TRANSACTION BETWEEN YOU AND ANY THIRD PARTY WEBSITE OR FOR ANY INFORMATION APPEARING ON THIRD PARTY WEBSITES.

INFORMATION COLLECTED FROM AND/OR SHARED WITH SOCIAL MEDIA SITES:

When accessing the Website through a third party social media site and/or application, we may access some of your information from your social media account, such as name, email address, profile picture, location, friend list, posts and/or likes. Please note that some aggregate information, that does not personally identify you, such as content viewed on the social media site/application, may also be collected by us if you access the Website through a third party social media site.

CHANGING, UPDATING OR REMOVING YOUR INFORMATION:

You may update, correct or remove your personal information at any time and free of charge by contacting us at info@noahny.com. We may ask that you identify yourself and the information you wish to access, change or delete for security purposes, and we will comply with your request as soon as reasonably practicable. By removing some of your information, you may not be able to access some of the Website’s features. We may keep some of your personal information if required by law and/or for recordkeeping purposes. 

OPT-OUTING OF OUR NEWSLETTER AND EMAIL COMMUNICATIONS:

You may unsubscribe from any marketing communications by clicking on the “Unsubscribe” button included in all of our marketing communications or by contacting us at info@noahny.com.

RIGHTS OF CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS:

Pursuant to California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with the California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE 1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by telephone at (916) 445-1254 or (800) 952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: www.ftc.gov.

If you are a resident of California, you may request that we not share your information with certain affiliates or third parties providers for marketing purposes, and/or you may inquire as to how we have shared your information with third parties providers for marketing purposes. In connection with such request, we will identify the types of information shared and provide you with the names and addresses of the third parties with whom the information was shared. If you would like to receive any such information, please contact us at info@noahny.com.

Do Not Track Signals

Our Website does not recognize Do Not Track signals. Some third parties may collect aggregate information about the users’ online activities over time and across websites when they use the Website. While this information does not include personally identifiable information, certain processing activities that combine aggregate information with other information in possession of such third parties could result in the identification of users.

CHILDREN’S RIGHTS:

While we do not sell products or services for purchase by children, we may sell children’s products or services for purchase by adults. If you are under 18 years old, you may use the Website only under the supervision of a parent or guardian. In accordance with the Federal Children's Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA), we do not knowingly collect, solicit or use personal information of children under the age of 13 provided without parental consent. Should we become aware that a user under the age of 13 has registered without verifiable parental consent, any such information will be deleted.

UPDATES TO OUR PRIVACY POLICY:

Noah Clothing LLC may amend or update all or any portion of this Privacy Policy, at any time, without notice, in its sole discretion. Please access this section regularly to verify if any changes were made to our Privacy Policy and to review the updated Privacy Policy.

EFFECTIVE DATE

This Privacy Policy is effective as of 5/16/2019.
